http://www.tiffanyrose.com/maternity/info/privacy.html

Shop Occasionwear at Alie Street
Shop our new occasion wear label, Alie Street London.
UK (£ GBP)
020 8397 0001
|
Choose Country / Currency
UK & Ireland:
UK / £ GBP
Ireland / € EUR
Europe:
Rest of Europe / € EUR
USA & Canada:
USA / US$
Canada / CA$
Rest of World:
Australia / AU$
Hong Kong / HK$
Rest of World / US$
Your Shopping Bag:
2013 & 2018
UK (£ GBP)
Maternity Coats
Shop All - Maternity Dresses »
Lookbook Autumn/Winter 2020-21 »
Bridal Face Masks
Shop All - Maternity Bridal »
Lookbook Autumn/Winter 2020-21 »
About Us
As Seen On...
Maternity Wedding Guest Outfits
Shop All - Maternity Dresses »
Lookbook Autumn/Winter 2020-21 »
The Naomi Collection
Shop All - Nursing Dresses »
Bridal Face Masks
Shop All - Maternity Bridal »
Lookbook Autumn/Winter 2020-21 »
Checkout
Designed & Made In BritainRead More »
FREE UK Shipping, Easy Returns
Delivery Information »
Superb Customer Service
Read Our Reviews »
Privacy Policy
Tiffany Rose takes our commitment to protecting your privacy seriously, and we treat any information you provide us with care. By visting our website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in our Privacy Policy below.
About Tiffany Rose Ltd
What Information We Collect
How We Use Your Information
Data Security
3rd Parties
Cookies
Contact Us
About Tiffany Rose Ltd
This Website is operated by Tiffany Rose Ltd ("Tiffany Rose", "We", "Us"), a company registered in England and Wales (Company No. 6893999) with a registered office at
2 Villiers Court, 40 Upper Mulgrave Road, Surrey, SM2 7AJ. Our Head Office address for all correspondence is:
Tiffany Rose Ltd
Typhoon Building
Oakcroft Road
Chessington
SURREY
KT9 1RH
United Kingdom
What Information We Collect
When you place an order with us we collect various information including your name, address, phone number, email address and credit/debit card details.
We collect information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.
We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.
How We Use Your Information
We will ONLY use the information that we collect about you lawfully and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
We will NOT e-mail you for marketing purposes unless you have given us your consent.
We will ALWAYS give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us in the future.
We will NOT pass your details to any Third Parties for marketing purposes.
Data Security
The personal information which we hold (either directly or on our behalf by third parties such as payment gateways or merchant service providers) will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and any standards imposed by law, including PCI DSS.
Third Parties
In order to complete your order we will need to disclose some of your information (for example your Name and Address) to our delivery partners including Royal Mail, DHL, DPD and their affiliates.
Cookies
In order to operate our Website we use technology known as a 'cookies', which store anonymous information relating to your Internet activity (such as whether you have visited our Website before, or placed items into your Shopping Bag) on your computer so that we can use this information to carry out your Order and improve our Website.
We also use online tools from Google called Analytics to understand how customers use our website and to provide a better service to you. This tool may involve setting (anonymous) cookies in your web browser. Click here for more information on Google's Privacy Policy.
If you do not wish for us to store cookies when you use our Website please adjust your Internet browser settings - the "Help" option on the menu bar of your web browser should explain you how to do this. However, please note that Our Website requires that cookies are enabled in order for you to place an Order so we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Most modern Internet browsers (including Internet Explorer 8.0 and above, Mozilla Firefox 4.0 and above, and Google Chrome) include the option to run in a mode which does not leave cookies on your computer after you leave a website. You may wish to enable this mode without affecting your use of our Website. This mode is known as "InPrivate Filtering" in Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and "Incognito" in Google Chrome. See the "Help" section of your Internet browser for more details.
Contact Us
The information we hold will be kept accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.
If you have any questions/comments about privacy, please email us.
Follow Tiffany Rose
Be the first to know
Get the latest news about exclusive specials and insider style advice. Sign up to receive our newsletter.
© 2002-2020 Tiffany Rose Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
follow us...
Express Shipping via:
Visit Our International Sites
Copyright
© 2002-2020 Tiffany Rose Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Company No. 6893999 | VAT Registered GB 805767804
|  Terms and Conditions
|  Privacy Policy
